<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="lz_definition_question">List the main livelihood zones in the county according to the main source of income for the majority of households living in that zone. A single livelihood zone is one in which the majority of people have a similar way of life, including economic opportunities, economic activities, and cultural and social practices. Ensure that the classification that you use includes all parts of the county.
</string>
    <string name="location_and_population_question">In the table below fill out proportion of the total population that belong to the various wealth groups. Describe the basic characteristics used to define each group e.g number of livestock, income, land holding etc.</string>
    <string name="lz_crop_production_question">In the table below, include all crops, both cash crops and food crops that are grown in the area. Provide a breakdown of crop cultivation in the area, by giving the approximate percentage of the cultivated area in the LZ that is covered by each crop and by fallow and fodder crops. Also estimate the approximate average yield in kilograms per hectare. Also provide a rough estimate of the percentage of the area that is under irrigation in each season.</string>
    <string name="lz_crop_production_question_section_two">Try to use specific crop names (like “haricot bean” or “wheat”) instead of general categories (like “pulses” or “cereals”). Include all crops that are grown in significant quantities. Consider your answers for a “normal” year, in which growing conditions are neither exceptionally good, nor exceptionally bad.</string>
    <string name="lz_water_source_question">In the table below, estimate the percentage of the total population in the livelihood zone depending on the listed water sources</string>
    <string name="lz_hunger_patterns">In the space provided, in how many years in the last ten years have the majority of people experienced hunger, or required food assistance to avert widespread hunger?</string>
    <string name="lz_hazards_question">In the table below, provide information on the main hazards in the LZ, i.e., the factors that have created the most human suffering in terms of mortality, hunger, morbidity and economic hardship. Rank them in importance from 1 (most important, highest risk) to 20 (least important, lowest impact) and estimate how many times they have occurred in the last 10 years.</string>
    <string name="lz_markets_question">Enter the names of the main markets used by people living in the livelihood zone, the name of the nearest town or village and county/subcounty where the market is located. Indicate which types of product are traded, by circling ‘yes’ or ‘no’. Include markets in other counties, if these are used.</string>
    <string name="ethnicity_question">In the table below, provide a rough breakdown of the population by ethnic group, i.e., what percentage of the population of the LZ belongs to each ethnic group. Check the totals add up to 100.</string>
    <string name="lz_sublocation_assignment">Below is a table showcasing all the sub-locations under the livelihood zone you selected at the initial stage of the questionnaire. This is not a question but rather a presentation for your own appreciation. If you however identify a sub-location that is wrongly classified, kindly contact the admin.</string>
</resources>

